[TH] Maria:
I grew up in a fishing town much like this one,
[TH] in a small South American country
you probably never heard of...
[TH] But that village is long
gone, after a battle between
[TH] U.C.S.-friendly government
forces and guerrillas.
[TH] They destroyed everything...
My home, my family, everything I knew.
[TH] The guerrillas were the ones
who took me under their wing.
[TH] By the time I was fifteen, I
was fighting alongside them.
[TH] I fought the U.C.S. and their
cronies with all the rage I could muster.
[TH] That was all I had left, and all I knew.
[TH] In the end, we were crushed...
[TH] We were just a bunch of militants from
a backwards country it was inevitable.
[TH] The few of us that were left were captured
and sent back to the mainland for trial.
[TH] Maria:
And that's where he found me.
[TH] \NM00:
...Driscoll.
[TH] Maria:
Yes. He promised to save me from execution
[TH] if I agreed to work for him, as an agent.
[TH] If I had known...I would've
just spat in his face and laughed.
[TH] Driscoll wasn't even working
for the U.C.S. Day in and day out,
[TH] I lied, killed, and betrayed
those who would trust us.
[TH] All this for a goal that
only Driscoll knew.
[TH] He's the one who put me in
the Black Hounds, you know?
[TH] Maria:
I've been betraying you since the first day we met.
[TH] \NM00:
It doesn't matter now.
[TH] I can't pretend to understand what you've
gone through, or what you had to do...
[TH] \NM00:
But if you'll let me, I'll carry those burdens with you.
[TH] As long as I can be with you.
[TH] \NM00:
When I heard that you were still alive,
[TH] that's all I could think about
being with you, no matter what.
[TH] Maria:
Maybe...
[TH] Maybe I was waiting for
someone to tell me that all along.
[TH] You haven't changed, \NM00.
[TH] Even being beaten and battered
by the war didn't change you.
[TH] Maybe you're the
stronger of the two of us.
[TH] Maria:
Me, I'm just...I'm just so tired.
[TH] \NM00:
Rest if you're tired.
[TH] Repent if you've sinned.
[TH] Life lets us do that.
[TH] We can always start over.